

Karthik Reddy Pejjaye

BUSINESS DEVELOPMENT SPECIAL

As a highly qualified professional holding a Bachelor's degree in engineering and a Graduate Diploma degree in Business Management, coupled with over 9 years of hands-on experience in the corporate sector, I have adeptly absorbed diverse work cultures and honed my managerial skills in global business processes. I am enthusiastic about pursuing Senior Business Executive positions in the UAE.

reddykarthik.kr75@gmail.com



+971567541570



Abu Dhabi, UAE



in linkedin.com/in/pejjaye

WORK EXPERIENCE

Business Development Specialist Strategico FZ LLC - Yas Creative Hub.

06/2021 - Present

TwoFour54 Media & Entertainment, Abu Dhabi

Abu Dhabi

- Developed Internal Business Processes, Organizational Assets and project revenues for the organization. Expertise in upselling B2B digital media services & identifying prospective clients by providing marketing strategies to sales team.
- Instructed Digital Marketing Teams and guided the projects on delivering the business outcomes with the validated business objectives. Expert in maintaining Online Reputation Management for clients, infact developed the ORM media service from scratch as the organizational service.
- Developed Strategies for the organization in terms of Business Development and assisted the Director of "Marketing & Business Management" sector in analysis and following Management Accounting principles/techniques in business proposals.
- Services delivery & developing new services for the organization and in turn supporting Finance Department with invoices. Preparation of financial quotations, SLAs, contracts, and SOW documents for potential clients and project deals. Followups with client's contracts, closing SLA's up on successful completions & driving the extra mile towards customer retention.
- Assisting project managers on new strategies for customer satisfaction & customer retention using marketing techniques and business development tactics.
- Expert in UAE tender systems, bidding projects, applying for open tenders and submitting Financial & Strategic proposals to media sector client's in TMT industry.
- Supporting Senior Management in internal and external business analysis for decision-making reasoning on daily basis. Closely working with Finance team in periodically preparing estimations, forecasts, payments and invoices.
- Achieved project management rewards and gained extensive skills on portfolio management on the best quality of delivery by satisfying clients. Research & Developments with case studies, ideas of improving media & communication services in Technology, Media & Telecom industry.

Supply Chain Analyst

Woolworths Group of Companies-Countdown.

Christchurch, New Zealand

Accomplished targets as Health & Safety Rep as well as a Covid Coach 2020 for the company.

 Delivering Business level decision-making to the organization in the logistics chain by handling the company assets worth \$30M NZD in distributing over the south of New

Digital Marketing - Social Media Specialist intern English Express - NZIBT - New Zealand

03/2018 - 05/2018

Christchurch, New Zealand

Marketing & joining conversations on behalf of NZIBT by providing support to current and prospective customers and contributed more than 70% of the strategic approaches.

 Analyzed the responses and engaged the viewers at the right time with strategic approaches and managing changes based on the audience responses.

Contact: kingsley@nzibt.ac.nz - john@nzibt.ac.nz

Software Test Analyst - Programmer Analyst Cognizant Technology Solutions India Pvt. Ltd.

• Assisted Business Intelligence, Data Analysts and software testing; in providing meaningful information that drew scope for business expansions with respect to clients/customers in Agile environments. Got promoted as Test Lead in less than 2 Years under the leadership of Mr. Ragesh Mohanan(Sr. Manager)

Contact: Ragesh.mohanan@cognizant.com

SKILLS

Advanced Management Accounting-BI

Strategic Management and Managing Change

Microsoft Suite

Requirement Gathering and Closure

CERTIFICATES

 Customer 1st Champion (10/2020) Been a role model for the company in delivering and driving the B2B and in turn B2C at Woolworths NZ

EDUCATION

Bachelors in Chemical Engineering & Material Sciences (05/2010 - 06/2014)

Graduate Diploma in Business - Bachelors Eqv. (11/2017 - 11/2018)

New Zealand

BUSINESS STANDARDS

Balanced Score Card

Native or Bilingual Proficiency

RACI Matrix & Traceability Native or Bilingual Proficiency

Tender System Specialist Native or Bilingual Proficiency

Full Professional Proficiency

Google Data Studio/Power BI Native or Bilingual Proficiency

Applications Management Full Professional Proficiency